Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Zhiqiu.
تشيكيو.
Mr. Xiang,
السيد شيانغ،
let me take you somewhere.
دعني آخذك إلى مكان ما.
Where?
أين؟
You'll see when we get there.
سترى ذلك عندما نصل إلى هناك.
Child.
طفل.
Your father
والدك
is taking me to turn myself in.
هذا يدفعني لتسليم نفسي.
Xiangyang,
شيانغيانغ،
I've disappointed you again in the end.
لقد خيبت ظنك مرة أخرى في النهاية.
I'll turn myself in.
سأسلم نفسي.
But why
لكن لماذا؟
can't you give me six more months
ألا يمكنك أن تمنحني ستة أشهر أخرى؟
to have this baby?
أنجب هذا الطفل؟
Back to this place again.
سأعود إلى هذا المكان مرة أخرى.
That email,
تلك الرسالة الإلكترونية،
did you see it?
هل رأيته؟
What email?
أي بريد إلكتروني؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I'm not Ye Zhiqiu.
أنا لست يي تشي تشيو.
I've known for a long time.
أعرف ذلك منذ زمن طويل.
I thought
ظننت
I could fool you.
أستطيع أن أخدعك.
I just preferred to let myself be deceived.
فضّلتُ ببساطة أن أدع نفسي أُخدع.
Long ago,
منذ زمن بعيد،
I already sensed it.
لقد شعرت بذلك بالفعل.
You're not the one
أنت لست الشخص المناسب
who was hot and cold with me, Ye Zhiqiu.
كان يي تشي تشيو متقلب المزاج معي.
I don't know who you are.
لا أعرف من أنت.
I don't know why
أنا لا أعرف لماذا
you're pretending to be Ye Zhiqiu to get close to me
أنت تتظاهر بأنك يي تشي تشيو لتتقرب مني
or what your real purpose is.
أو ما هو هدفك الحقيقي.
But since you appeared in my life,
لكن منذ أن ظهرت في حياتي،
I've felt a sense of security I've never had before.
لقد شعرتُ بإحساس بالأمان لم أشعر به من قبل.
I'm becoming more and more addicted to this feeling.
أصبحتُ مدمناً على هذا الشعور أكثر فأكثر.
I don't want to know who you are anymore.
لا أريد أن أعرف من أنت بعد الآن.
Let's just say you're Ye Zhiqiu.
لنفترض أنك يي تشي تشيو.
Then do you know
هل تعلم؟
where the real Ye Zhiqiu is right now?
أين يي تشي تشيو الحقيقي الآن؟
I don't want to know anymore.
لا أريد أن أعرف المزيد.
No.
لا.
You must know.
يجب أن تعلم.
Do you know
هل تعلم
how Rachel died?
كيف ماتت راشيل؟
How Shelly died?
كيف ماتت شيلي؟
And Shi Xiaodi?
وشي شياو دي؟
It doesn't matter if you didn't see that email.
لا يهم إن لم تكن قد رأيت تلك الرسالة الإلكترونية.
I can tell you myself.
أستطيع أن أخبرك بنفسي.
I don't want to hear anymore.
لا أريد أن أسمع المزيد.
They're all
جميعهم
with Ye Zhiqiu now,
مع Ye Zhiqiu الآن،
lying in a dark, sunless underground place.
مستلقياً في مكان مظلم تحت الأرض، بلا شمس.
Please stop talking about this.
من فضلك توقف عن الحديث عن هذا الموضوع.
Their deaths have nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك بوفاتهم.
How can they have nothing to do with me?
كيف لا يكون لهم أي علاقة بي؟
Ye Zhiqiu's death was an accident,
كانت وفاة Ye Zhiqiu حادثًا.
but everything that happened afterward spiraled out of control.
لكن كل ما حدث بعد ذلك خرج عن السيطرة.
I am the unforgivable criminal.
أنا المجرم الذي لا يغتفر له.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I know
أنا أعرف
all these people were killed by Leng Xiaoxiao.
كل هؤلاء الأشخاص قُتلوا على يد لينغ شياو شياو.
From the first time I saw the surveillance footage,
منذ اللحظة الأولى التي شاهدت فيها لقطات المراقبة،
I already knew there was someone
كنت أعرف مسبقاً أن هناك شخصاً ما
who looked exactly like Ye Zhiqiu.
الذي كان يشبه تماماً يي تشي تشيو.
I just never thought
لم يخطر ببالي أبداً
that person would be Leng Xiaoxiao.
ذلك الشخص هو لينغ شياو شياو.
I should have talked Xiaoxiao out of it.
كان عليّ أن أقنع شياو شياو بالعدول عن ذلك.
I shouldn't have
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أفعل
let Xiaoxiao make one mistake after another.
دع شياو شياو ترتكب خطأً تلو الآخر.
If I had been a little braver,
لو كنت أكثر شجاعة قليلاً،
if I had turned myself in earlier,
لو كنت قد سلمت نفسي في وقت سابق،
if I had ended all this sooner,
لو كنت قد أنهيت كل هذا في وقت أبكر،
perhaps
ربما
Xiaoxiao and the others wouldn't have died.
ما كان ليموت شياو شياو والآخرون.
But, Xiangyang,
ولكن، شيانغيانغ،
I'm pregnant.
أنا حامل.
The doctor says
يقول الطبيب
he's developing well.
إنه يتطور بشكل جيد.
He's already formed.
لقد تشكل بالفعل.
Could you
يمكنك
give me another six months?
أعطني ستة أشهر أخرى؟
Let me give birth to him.
دعني ألده.
Then I'll turn myself in.
ثم سأسلم نفسي.
Okay?
تمام؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I thought I was someone who knew right from wrong.
كنت أظن أنني شخص يعرف الصواب من الخطأ.
But until I met you,
لكن قبل أن ألتقي بك،
until I fell in love with you,
حتى وقعت في حبك،
I abandoned all my previous moral principles.
لقد تخليت عن جميع مبادئي الأخلاقية السابقة.
Even though you were once my friend's wife,
مع أنكِ كنتِ زوجة صديقي في يوم من الأيام،
I still selfishly want to have you for myself.
ما زلت أرغب، بدافع أناني، في الحصول عليكِ لنفسي.
I blame myself for Hong Ming's death,
ألوم نفسي على وفاة هونغ مينغ،
yet I'm hopelessly lost in your tenderness.
ومع ذلك، فأنا تائه تماماً في حنانك.
I can ignore all the gossip in the world.
بإمكاني تجاهل كل القيل والقال في العالم.
I just want to be with you.
أريد فقط أن أكون معك.
Xie Yuxuan,
شيه يوكسوان,
can we give each other a chance?
هل يمكننا أن نمنح بعضنا البعض فرصة؟
But I can't do it.
لكنني لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
I can't
لا أستطبع
put all the blame
ألقي باللوم كله
on Xiaoxiao.
على شياو شياو.
Xiangyang,
شيانغيانغ،
I want to end all this.
أريد أن أنهي كل هذا.
I want to atone for my sins.
أريد أن أكفّر عن ذنوبي.
I want to turn myself in.
أريد أن أسلم نفسي.
But our child...
لكن طفلنا...
Then let's have the baby first.
فلننجب الطفل أولاً.
No matter what happens in the future,
بغض النظر عما سيحدث في المستقبل،
I will always stay by your side.
سأبقى دائماً بجانبك.
Now we'll start counting down.
والآن سنبدأ العد التنازلي.
You will slowly wake up.
ستستيقظ ببطء.
You know that everything that just happened
أنت تعلم أن كل ما حدث للتو
was just a dream.
كان مجرد حلم.
You want to wake up from this dream.
تريد أن تستيقظ من هذا الحلم.
Your body is slowly regaining consciousness.
جسمك يستعيد وعيه ببطء.
Your hand moved.
تحركت يدك.
Everything in the hypnotic trance
كل شيء في حالة النشوة التنويمية
hasn't happened yet.
لم يحدث ذلك بعد.
You can choose your life path again.
يمكنك اختيار مسار حياتك مرة أخرى.
Now,
الآن،
you're about to wake up
أنت على وشك الاستيقاظ
and return to the present.
والعودة إلى الحاضر.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
I saw...
رأيت...
I spread rumors about how Xiangyang hurt me.
لقد نشرت شائعات حول كيف آذاني شيانغيانغ.
My father, to protect me,
أبي، لحمايتي،
endlessly insulted Xiangyang.
أهان شيانغيانغ بلا هوادة.
The relationship between the Leng family and Xiangyang got worse and worse.
تدهورت العلاقة بين عائلة لينغ وشيانغيانغ أكثر فأكثر.
Dad finally had a heart attack from anger and passed away.
أصيب أبي بنوبة قلبية من شدة الغضب وتوفي.
I fell into a pit of hatred.
لقد سقطت في هاوية الكراهية.
I dragged my best friend into endless revenge.
لقد جررت صديقي المقرب إلى انتقام لا ينتهي.
In the end, I lost everything
في النهاية، خسرت كل شيء
and became what I hated most.
وأصبح ما كنت أكرهه أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Do you really have to do this?
هل أنت مضطر حقاً لفعل هذا؟
Is there a better choice?
هل يوجد خيار أفضل؟
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Sis,
نعم،
why didn't you go back home?
لماذا لم تعد إلى المنزل؟
My mom was in a car accident two weeks ago.
تعرضت والدتي لحادث سيارة قبل أسبوعين.
She had surgery that same day.
أجرت عملية جراحية في نفس اليوم.
She's still recovering now.
لا تزال تتعافى حتى الآن.
It happened that afternoon after leaving your place.
حدث ذلك بعد ظهر ذلك اليوم بعد مغادرتك لمنزلك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
what are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I haven't been sleeping well lately.
لم أنم جيداً في الآونة الأخيرة.
I came to get some medication
جئت لأحصل على بعض الأدوية
and have hypnotherapy.
ويخضع للعلاج بالتنويم الإيحائي.
Hypnotherapy?
العلاج بالتنويم الإيحائي؟
It's like
الأمر أشبه
I've been in a dream.
لقد كنت في حلم.
And now I've woken up.
والآن استيقظت.
Only then did I realize
عندها فقط أدركت
how to live a better life.
كيف تعيش حياة أفضل.
Sis.
أخت.
Buy some good food for Mom
اشتري بعض الطعام الجيد للأم
and get the best medicine.
واحصل على أفضل دواء.
Don't tell Xiangyang I was here.
لا تخبر شيانغيانغ أنني كنت هنا.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
We're going through a divorce.
نحن نمر بمرحلة الطلاق.
Divorce?
الطلاق؟
Is it because of me and Mom?
هل هذا بسببي أنا وأمي؟
No, Xiaoxiao, let me tell you.
لا يا شياو شياو، دعيني أخبرك.
Xiangyang is a filial child.
شيانغيانغ طفل بار بوالديه.
He knows Mom had an accident
هو يعلم أن والدته تعرضت لحادث
at the entrance of your neighborhood,
عند مدخل حيّك،
and he feels extremely guilty about it.
ويشعر بذنب شديد حيال ذلك.
That's why he's being temperamental.
ولهذا السبب هو متقلب المزاج.
Don't divorce him because of this.
لا تطلقيه بسبب هذا.
Sis.
أخت.
I'm at fault too.
أنا مخطئ أيضاً.
I've never
لم يسبق لي أن
considered things from Xiangyang's perspective.
أخذ الأمور بعين الاعتبار من منظور شيانغيانغ.
I've never cared about his feelings either.
لم أهتم بمشاعره قط.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Take good care of Mom.
اعتني بأمك جيداً.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Honey.
عسل.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Weren't you on a business trip?
ألم تكن في رحلة عمل؟
Why are you back so soon?
لماذا عدت بهذه السرعة؟
Because I missed you.
لأنني اشتقت إليك.
It's broad daylight, aren't you in a hurry?
إنه نهار ساطع، ألا تشعر بالعجلة؟
Hurry up.
أسرع.
I made plans with Xiaoxiao to see Zhiqiu's concert.
لقد رتبت مع شياو شياو لحضور حفل تشي تشيو.
How can I rush something like this?
كيف يمكنني تسريع أمر كهذا؟
If I rush, how could you enjoy it?
إذا استعجلت، فكيف ستستمتع به؟
Honey.
عسل.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
We're going to be late.
سنتأخر.
Coming.
آت.
How do I look in this outfit?
كيف أبدو بهذا الزي؟
Beautiful.
جميل.
My wife
زوجتي
looks gorgeous in anything.
تبدو رائعة في أي شيء.
You're such a sweet talker.
أنتِ بارعة في الكلام المعسول.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Rachel.
رايتشل.
I wouldn't be who I am today without you.
ما كنت لأكون ما أنا عليه اليوم لولاك.
I'm looking forward
أتطلع إلى ذلك
to stepping into the next decade with you.
لنبدأ العقد القادم معكم.
I hope
آمل
you'll always be my comrade through thick and thin,
ستظل رفيقي في السراء والضراء،
my closest friend.
صديقي المقرب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you for being here.
شكراً لحضوركم.
At the same time,
وفي الوقت نفسه،
I'd also like to thank my dear classmates.
أود أيضاً أن أشكر زملائي الأعزاء في الدراسة.
Thank you all for coming today
شكراً لكم جميعاً على حضوركم اليوم
to witness my next decade.
لأشهد العقد القادم من حياتي.
Thank you all.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
I love you all.
أحبكم جميعاً.
Why didn't Xiangyang come today?
لماذا لم يأتِ شيانغيانغ اليوم؟
He's busy.
إنه مشغول.
Hongming didn't come either.
لم يأتِ هونغمينغ أيضاً.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Am I late?
هل تأخرت؟
Is it all over?
هل انتهى كل شيء؟
You two talk. I'll go find Hongming.
تحدثا أنتما الاثنان. سأذهب لأبحث عن هونغمينغ.
Bye.
الوداع.
I thought you
ظننتك
didn't want to see your first love,
لم أرغب برؤية حبك الأول،
Ye Zhiqiu.
أيها تشي تشيو.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
You're the only one in my heart.
أنت الوحيد في قلبي.
This is a gift I brought you from Europe.
هذه هدية أحضرتها لك من أوروبا.
You'll definitely like it.
ستعجبك بالتأكيد.
You shouldn't have spent so much.
كان عليك ألا تنفق كل هذا المبلغ.
Come over here.
تعال إلى هنا.
Limited edition.
إصدار محدود.
Good taste.
ذوق رفيع.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
During my trip to Europe,
خلال رحلتي إلى أوروبا،
I met with David.
التقيت بديفيد.
He's very interested in our products.
إنه مهتم جداً بمنتجاتنا.
If we can convince Dad
إذا استطعنا إقناع أبي
to make some minor adjustments
لإجراء بعض التعديلات الطفيفة
to our existing products,
إلى منتجاتنا الحالية،
David will definitely agree.
سيوافق ديفيد بالتأكيد.
I understand.
أفهم.
Dad never listened to your suggestions before.
لم يستمع أبي إلى اقتراحاتك من قبل.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I'll be the mediator between you two.
سأكون الوسيط بينكما.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
You've worked hard too.
لقد بذلت جهدًا كبيرًا أيضًا.
Let's go eat.
هيا بنا نأكل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mom, are you okay?
أمي، هل أنتِ بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Take some time to rest when you get home.
خذ بعض الوقت للراحة عند عودتك إلى المنزل.
Make sure to remind Mom to take her medicine on time.
تأكد من تذكير والدتك بتناول دوائها في الوقت المحدد.
Don't worry. I can take good care of Mom.
لا تقلق. سأعتني بأمي جيداً.
Xiaoxiao came to the hospital a while ago.
وصلت شياو شياو إلى المستشفى منذ فترة.
Did you know?
هل تعلم؟
She didn't tell me.
لم تخبرني.
She didn't mention it.
لم تذكر ذلك.
Mom.
أم.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
I'm here to take you home from the hospital.
أنا هنا لأخذك إلى المنزل من المستشفى.
Good.
جيد.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I cut my finger.
جرحت إصبعي.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
You're still smiling?
ما زلت تبتسم؟
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Press on it first.
اضغط عليه أولاً.
How can you be so happy when you're hurt?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون سعيداً جداً وأنت مجروح؟
Seeing you so serious
رؤيتك بهذه الجدية
is really amusing.
إنه أمر مسلٍ حقاً.
You're making lamb with scallions for me?
هل ستعدين لي لحم الضأن مع البصل الأخضر؟
Why didn't you ask my sister to help you?
لماذا لم تطلب من أختي مساعدتك؟
I wanted to surprise you.
أردت أن أفاجئك.
I don't want to bother your sister for everything.
لا أريد أن أزعج أختك في كل شيء.
I don't want your mother to think
لا أريد أن تعتقد والدتك
that I can't do anything.
أنني لا أستطيع فعل أي شيء.
She might feel sorry for you then.
قد تشعر بالشفقة عليك حينها.
But you've never
لكنك لم تفعل ذلك قط
set foot in a kitchen your entire life.
ضع قدمك في المطبخ طوال حياتك.
All this time,
طوال هذا الوقت،
you've been the one making sacrifices for me.
لقد كنت أنت من يقدم التضحيات من أجلي.
But love should be a two-way street.
لكن الحب يجب أن يكون متبادلاً.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
I love you.
أحبك.
I love you too.
أحبك أيضًا.
- Row.
- صف.